Terrell C. Lombardi

Schmidtstrasse 30 | -65385 Rüdesheim am Rhein +49 151 65227520 tcl71771@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/terry-c-lombardi/ https://terrell-lombardi.de



Full Stack Web Developer

Technically experienced manager with expertise in software development projects.

Qualification profile

Functional and cost-oriented project manager. Agile manager of interdisciplinary and intercultural specialists. Innovative and analytical process optimizer and potential butterfly. Passionate and empathetic project specialist with assertive negotiation skills. Decisive requirements and stakeholder manager.

Competences

- Programming
- Data Visualization
- Web Ethics
- Data Security
- Test-Driven Development
- Databases
- Web Design
- Web Accessibility
- · Testing and Debugging
- Web Hosting

Training

Full Stack Web Development 09/2021 – today CareerFoundry

General Liberal Arts AA 2004

Pensacola Junior College, Pensacola, FL

Selection of projects

- Development of a Pokemon-oriented web application called PokeDex App that uploads data from an external API to facilitate a more detailed view of data points.
- ✓ Development of the film app "MyFlix" with the aim of building a server-based component that provides users with information regarding films, directors and genres.

Professional career

Managing Owner10/2014 - today
Marketing Solid Foundations, LLC Mebane, NC

Strategic and operational management and responsibility for \$1.8 million in revenue. Determination of optimization and development opportunities as well as their implementation for value preservation. Establishment and further development of a high-performance organization appropriate to the business model and volume. Establishment and maintenance of active business relationships with operational partners and target contacts. Implementation of a future-oriented corporate strategy. Development and implementation of revenue-increasing and innovative measures.

- Significant increase in revenue of approximately \$50T per month
- Development of the community outreach program that meets the needs of the city
- Development and implementation of an annual business plan and customer service manual

Branch Manager / Vice President / Bank Official07/2012 - 10/2014 SunTrust Bank HillSborough, NC

Management of sales activities in the store in the course of the power of attorney. Carrying out daily coordination and checks. Responsibility and development of a team of up to 15 employees. Fast, competent and friendly handling of all customer concerns. Management, opening and administration of customers. Monitoring and meeting targets. Customer acquisition and customer service. Area responsibility of the insurance business.

Establishment of the branch as the most profitable branch in the region

TerrEll C. Lombardi | Side 2

Apria Healthcare, Inc. Morrisville, NC

Coordination and clarification of open items. Order and booking of incoming payments and clarification of any payment differences. Conducting credit checkers and monitoring the credit limit. Contact person for domestic and foreign customers, as well as interface function to internal departments for customer inquiries. Handling of correspondence with debt collection agencies and insolvency administrators as well as preparation of the recapitulative statement.

- Execution of over 350 transactions per hour with a mandatory minimum number of transactions of 110 transactions per hour
- Successful implementation of new transaction processing strategies
- Processing all medical claims from all 50 states and Federal Medicare as the only person on the company

Additional experience

Freelance programmer | Various clients

Various administrative positions | Mega Force Sanford / Brickcity Community Church Sanford / Lee County Sanford Tax Administration

Website Moderator/Editor | Pensacola

Operations Manager | CompUSA Ft Walton Beach

Managing Director | CyberZone Pensacola

New and Used Car Manager - Financial Manager | Mitchell Nissan-Mazda Enterprise / Victor Nissan Selma

Training and certifications

Full-Stack Immersion | CareerFoundry (2021) Intro to Frontend Development | CareerFoundry (2021)

IT skills and languages

MS Office | Basic | nBasic | Pascal | Cobal | Fortran | Turbo Pascal | | JavaScript Web Server Frameworks | Node.js | HTML | CSS | CSS Grid | CSS Flexbox | GitHub | Version Control | MongoDB | React Native | Express.JS | React | Angular | Postman German, level | English, mother tongue

Rüdesheim am Rhein, 27. September 2022

Terrell C. Lombardi